export const QUESTIONS = [
  {
    name: 'question_1',
    type: 'list',
    questionText: 'JavaScript was created in 10 days then released on\n',
    choices: [
      'May 23rd, 1995',
      'Nov 24th, 1995',
      'Dec 4th, 1995',
      'Dec 17, 1996',
    ],
    answer: 'Dec 4th, 1995',
  },
  {
    name: 'question_2',
    type: 'list',
    questionText: 'Which of the following is not a JavaScript framework?\n',
    choices: ['Angular', 'React', 'Vue', 'Laravel'],
    answer: 'Laravel',
  },
  {
    name: 'question_3',
    type: 'list',
    questionText: "What is the difference between '==' and '==='?\n",
    choices: [
      "'==' checks for value equality and '===' checks for value and type equality",
      "'==' checks for value and type equality and '===' checks for value equality",
      "'==' checks for value equality and '===' checks for value equality",
      "'==' checks for value and type equality and '===' checks for value and type equality",
    ],
    answer:
      "'==' checks for value equality and '===' checks for value and type equality",
  },
  {
    name: 'question_4',
    type: 'checkbox',
    questionText: 'Which of the following are JavaScript data types?\n',
    choices: [
      'Number',
      'String',
      'Enum',
      'Boolean',
      'Object',
      'Array',
      'Function',
    ],
    answer: ['Number', 'String', 'Boolean', 'Object', 'Array', 'Function'],
  },
  {
    name: 'question_5',
    type: 'list',
    questionText: 'Which of the following is not a JavaScript operator?\n',
    choices: ['new', 'this', 'delete', 'typeof'],
    answer: 'this',
  },
  {
    name: 'question_6',
    type: 'list',
    questionText: 'What is the output of `0.1 + 0.2 === 0.3`?\n',
    choices: ['true', 'false'],
    answer: 'false',
  },
  {
    name: 'question_7',
    type: 'list',
    questionText: 'What is hoisting in JavaScript?\n',
    choices: [
      'Moving variable and function declarations to the top of their scope',
      'Moving variable and function declarations to the bottom of their scope',
      'Moving variable and function declarations to the middle of their scope',
      'Moving variable and function declarations to the top of their scope and initializing them with undefined',
    ],
    answer:
      'Moving variable and function declarations to the top of their scope',
  },
  {
    name: 'question_8',
    type: 'input',
    questionText: "What is JavaScript's runtime environment called?\n",
    answer: 'nodejs',
  },
  {
    name: 'question_9',
    type: 'list',
    questionText: 'What is the output of 1 + "1"?\n',
    choices: ['11', '2', 'undefined', 'NaN'],
    answer: '11',
  },
  {
    name: 'question_10',
    type: 'list',
    questionText: 'What does `apply` do in JavaScript?\n',
    choices: [
      'It calls a function with a given `this` value and arguments provided as an array',
      'It calls a function with a given `this` value and arguments provided as an object',
      'It calls a function with a given `this` value and arguments provided as a string',
      'It calls a function with a given `this` value and arguments provided as a number',
    ],
    answer:
      'It calls a function with a given `this` value and arguments provided as an array',
  },
  {
    name: 'question_11',
    type: 'list',
    questionText: "What is chrome's runtime environment called?\n",
    choices: ['nodejs', 'v8', 'v12', 'spidermonkey'],
    answer: 'v8',
  },
  {
    name: 'question_12',
    type: 'list',
    questionText: 'What is the output of `typeof typeof 1`?\n',
    choices: ['number', 'string', 'undefined', 'NaN'],
    answer: 'string',
  },
];
